Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
MS 159
Colby, Clint.
This collection of little magazines was assembled over a period of several years. For purposes of this collection little magazines were defined as having primary emphasis on the arts; magazines with primary emphasis on politics---sexual, racial, economic, etc.--- were excluded from the collection.
25 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Acquired as gift and purchase, 1979.
Historical Note
This collection of little magazines was assembled over a period of several years. For purposes of this collection little magazines were defined as having primary emphasis on the arts; magazines with primary emphasis on politics---sexual, racial, economic, etc.--- were excluded from the collection. It will be found that a majority of these magazines are primarily or exclusively devoted to poetry. The collection is a sampling, both of little magazines as a group and of any specific magazines.
Arrangement
This collection is organized alphabetically by title.
Scope and Content Note
Collection consists of single issues, partial and complete runs of approximately 615 little magazines, published chiefly from 1965 to 1976. Primary emphasis is on the arts, with the majority devoted to poetry. Most of the periodicals are published in the United States; other countries represented are Mexico, Ecuador, Colombia, Argentina, Venezuela, South Africa, Kenya, Australia, India, Norway, Great Britain, France, Germany, and Canada. Arizona publications include Poet's Calliope; The Desert Rune; and Changes.
Additional materials at MS 242.
Inventory available in the library.
Access Terms
American literature -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
American periodicals -- Specimens.
American poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
Canadian poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
English poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
Latin American poetry -- Periodicals.
Little magazines -- Specimens.
Poetry -- Collections -- Periodicals.
Container List
- The Above Ground Review, Durham, North Carolina, v. 2, #2, Spring, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abraxas, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 1, #1, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abraxas, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 1, #2, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Abraxas, Madison, Wisconsin, #5 (Anthology; Ithaca, New York), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Abraxas, Madison, Wisconsin, #6, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Abraxas, Madison, Wisconsin, #7, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Abraxas, Madison, Wisconsin, #9, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Academus, Mexico, #9-10, April, 1965-May, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Activist, Oberlin College, Oberlin Ohio, v. 8, #1, Fall (#20), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Adventures in Poetry, New York City, #3, January, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Adventures in Poetry, New York City, #7, February, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Adventures in Poetry, New York City, #8, Summer, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Aesop's Feast Magazine, West Lafayette, Indiana, v. 1, #2, January, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- afterbirth, Fairhaven College, Winter/Spring, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ailleurs, France, #4, September, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Aion, New York City, #1, December, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- air, Vancouver, Canada #1, January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- air, Vancouver, Canada, #4, July, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- air, Vancouver, Canada, #5, September, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- air, Vancouver, Canada, #6, November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- air, Vancouver, Canada, #8, March, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Alcheringa, New York City, #4, Autumn, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #2, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #3, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #4, May, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #5, January, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #6, August, 1969-September, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- aldebaran review, Berkeley, California, #11, December, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Aleph, Takoma Park, Maryland, v. 1, #1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- The Alien Critic, Portland, Oregon, v. 2, #3 (#6), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Alkahest: American College Poetry, Middletown, Connecticut, #3, Fall, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Allegany Poetry, Olean, New York, #3, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Alphabet, London, Ontario, Canada, #6, June, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Amalgamated Holding Company, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, v. 1, #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Amalgamated Holding Company, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Amalgamated Holding Company, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, v. 1, #3, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Amazing Grace, London, England, #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Amanophis, Belgium, #6, May, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- American Poetry Magazine, Wauwatosa, Wisconsin, v. 28, #4, November, 1947-December, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- American Poetry Magazine, Wauwatosa, Wisconsin, v. 30, #4, November, 1949-December, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- The Amphora, San Francisco, #2, Autumn, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- The Amphora, San Francisco, #3, Winter, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- The Amphora, San Francisco, #4-5, Spring/Summer, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- The Amphora, San Francisco, #6, Fall, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- The Amphora, San Francisco, #7, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Analecta, Demarest, New Jersey, #1, Fall, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Analecta, Demarest, New Jersey, v. 2, #1, Winter, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Analecta, Demarest, New Jersey, v. 2, #2, Spring, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Anamnesis, n.p., #1, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- The Anchor Review, Garden City, New York, #1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Ann Arbor Review, Ann Arbor, Michigan, #1, Winter, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- The Anona Wynn, Cambridge, England, June, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Anonym, Buffalo, New York, #5-6, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- another poetry magazine, Toronto, Canada, #1, June, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- another poetry magazine, Toronto, Canada, #2, Winter, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Ante, Los Angeles, v. 1, #3, Spring, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ante, Los Angeles, v. 2, #1, Winter, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Ante, Los Angeles, v. 2, #2, Spring, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Ante, Los Angeles, v. 3, #2, Summer, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Ante, Los Angeles, v. 3, #4, Winter, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- The Antigonish Review, Antigonish, Nova Scotia, Canada, #12, Winter, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Antinarcissus, Surrealist Conquest, San Francisco, #1, Summer, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- An Apparition of the Late J, San Francisco, #1(?), undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- An Apparition of the Late J, San Francisco, #3, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- An Apparition of the Late J, San Francisco, #5, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Approches, France, #4, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Ararat, New York City, v. 12, #1, Winter (#45), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Arion's Dolphin, Cambridge, Massachusetts, v. 1, #1, Autumn, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Ark, Royal College of Art, London, England, #20, Spring, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- The Arc River Review, Wichita, Kansas, v. 2, #3, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Arsenal, Surrealist Subversion, Chicago, #1, Autumn, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Artifax, Chatsworth, California, v. 1, #1, May, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- The Artist's Miscellany, Montezuma, New Mexico, #2, October, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- The Artist's Miscellany, Montezuma, New Mexico, #3, January, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- The Artist's Miscellany, Montezuma, New Mexico, #4, February, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- The Artist's View, San Francisco, #4, March, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Arts in Society, University of Wisconsin, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 5, #2, Summer/Fall, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Aspect, Somerville, Massachusetts, v. 10 (#54), January, 1974-February, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Aspect, Somerville, Massachusetts, #56, May, 1974-June, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Aspect, Somerville, Massachusetts, #63, July, 1975-August, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Aspects, Eugene, Oregon, #5, October, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Aspects, Eugene, Oregon, #10, August, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Asterisk, Spring, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Asterisk #12, Pratt Institute, Brooklyn, New York, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Athanor, New York City, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Athanor, New York City, #2, Fall, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Athanor, Clarkson, New York, #3, Summer/Fall, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Atom Mind, Syracuse, New York, v. 1, #4, Spring, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Atom Mind, Syracuse, New York, v. 2, #5, Summer, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Atom Mind, Syracuse, New York, v. 2, #7, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Attention Please, Broderick, California, v. 1, #3, October, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Audit, Buffalo, New York, v. 1, #4, Summer/Fall, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Audit, Buffalo, New York, v. 5, #2 (Blue Vents, John Koethe), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Audit, Buffalo, New York, v. 5, #3, May, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- avalanche, Berkeley, California, #1, Summer, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- avalanche, Berkeley, California, #4, Spring, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- avalanche, Berkeley, California, #5, Winter, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Axolotl, Oakland, California, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Back Roads, Cotati, California, #6, Summer, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Bardic Echoes, Grand Rapids, Michigan, v. 9, #4, December, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- The Bastian Review, Zebulon-on-Coon, Kentucky, #1, Fall, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Beatitude, San Francisco, #18, circa 1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- The Bennington Review, Bennington College, Bennington, Vermont, v. 1, #3, Summer, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
- The Bennington Review, Bennington College, Bennington, Vermont, v. 3, #1, Winter, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- The Bennington Review, Bennington College, Bennington, Vermont, v. 3, #2, Summer, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- The Bennington Review, Bennington College, Bennington, Vermont, v. 4, #1, Summer, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Berkeley: A Journal of Modern Culture, Berkeley, California, #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Berkeley: A Journal of Modern Culture, Berkeley, California, #4, July, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Berkeley: A Journal of Modern Culture, Berkeley, California, #5, December, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Berkeley: A Journal of Modern Culture, Berkeley, California, #9, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Berkeley Poets Co-operative, Berkeley, California, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Berkeley Poets Co-operative, Berkeley, California, #2, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Berkeley Poets Co-operative, Berkeley, California, #5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- The Berkeley Samisdat Review, San Jose, California, v. 2, #1, Spring, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 1, #1 (#691), December, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 1, #3 (#701), August, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 2, #1 (#711), October, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 2, #2 (#712), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 3, #1 (#721), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 4, #1, early mid-Spring, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- beyond baroque, Venice, California, v. 5, #6 (#741), November, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Biala, Prahan College of Advanced Education, Prahan, Australia, v. 1, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Big Boulevard, Long Beach, California, v. 1, #1, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Big Boulevard, Long Beach, California, v. 2, #2, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Big Boulevard, Long Beach, California, v. 2, #3, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Big Moon, Boulder Creek, California, v. 2, #1, Winter, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Big Moon, Boulder Creek, California, v. 2, #2, Spring, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #1, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #2, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #3, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #4, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #6, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #7, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Big Sky, Bolinas, California, #9, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Big Table, Chicago, #1, Spring, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Big Table, Chicago, #2, Summer, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Big Table, Chicago, v. 1, #3, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Big Table, Chicago, v. 1, #4, Spring, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Big Table, Chicago, v. 2, #5, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Birth, New York City, #3, books 1-2, Autumn, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- The Bitter Oleander, Syracuse, New York, v. 1, #2, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Bitterroot, Brooklyn, New York, v. 11, #1, Fall (#41), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Bizarre, France, #1, May, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Bizarre, France, #2, October, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Blackfish, Burnaby, British Columbia, Canada, #2, Fall, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Bleating Hearts, Geyserville, California, February, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Bleb, New York City, #1, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Blue Grass, Dobbs Ferry, New York, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Blue Horse, Augusta, Georgia, v. 2 (Redivivus Blue Horse), 1966-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Blue Pig, Paris, France, #9 (Buri Cheese), January, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Blue Pig, Paris, France, #10 (No Eating), undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Blue Suede Shoes, Bellingham, Washington, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Blue Suede Shoes, Bellingham, Washington, v. 1, #4, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Blue Suede Shoes, Monterey, California, #6, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Blue Suede Shoes, Monterey, California, #9, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Blue Suede Shoes, Monterey, California, #11, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Blue Suede Shoes, Monterey, California, #13, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Bo Heem E Um, Sherborne, England, #3, January, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Bo Heem E Um, Sherborne, England, #4, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Bo Heem E Um, Sherborne, England, #5, December, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Bones, New York City, #3, Spring, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- The Book Review, San Francisco, #15, November, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- The Book Review, San Francisco, #16, December, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The Book Review, San Francisco, #18, March, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Boreal, Montreal, Canada, #5-6, February, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- The Boston Review of the Arts, Boston, v. 2, #6, September, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Box 749, New York City, v. 1, #4, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- The Brand New Testament, Monterey Peninsula College, Monterey, California, portfolio, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Bread &, New York City, #1, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Breakthru, Haynards Heath, England, v. 3, #16, May, 1964-June, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Breakthru, Haynards Heath, England, v. 4, #19, November, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Breakthru, Haynards Heath, England, v. 8, #47, July, 1964-August, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Bridge, Coconut Grove, Florida, v. 1, #4, Spring/Summer, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- The Bridge, Los Angeles, #1, Summer, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- "Brittanni, Buffalo, New York, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Brilliant Corners, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California, June, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Brilliant Corners, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California, June, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Brown Sweater, Eugene, Oregon, #2, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Brupa, Sacramento, California, v. 1, #1, circa 1969 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Brushfire, University of Nevada, Reno, Nevada, May, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Buckle, State University College, Buffalo, New York, v. 1, #1, Fall, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Busara, University College, Nairobi, Kenya, v. 2, #1, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Busara, University College, Nairobi, Kenya, v. 2, #2, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- cacophony, Bromsgrove, England, #2, December, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- cacophony, Bromsgrove, England, #3, February, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- caim, Baltimore, v. 2, #1, Fall, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- California Quarterly, University of California, Davis, California, #2, Summer, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- California Quarterly, University of California, Davis, California, #3, Autumn, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- California Quarterly, University of California, Davis, California, #4, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- California Review, Santa Barbara, California, #3, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- The Camel, the Lion, and the Child, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 1, #1, November, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- the camels hump, Reno, Nevada, #1, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- the camels hump, Reno, Nevada, #5, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- camels coming, Albuquerque, New Mexico, #1, August, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- camels coming, Reno, Nevada, #2, September, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- camels coming, Reno, Nevada, #3, October, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- camels coming, Reno, Nevada, #5, August, 1966-September, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- camels coming, Reno, Nevada, #6, December, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- camels coming, Reno, Nevada, #7, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- camels coming, Reno, Nevada, #8-9, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- camels coming newsletter (or camels coming, second series, San Francisco, #1, May, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- camels coming newsletter (or camels coming, second series, San Francisco, #2, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- camels coming newsletter (or camels coming, second series, San Francisco, #3, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- camels coming newsletter (or camels coming, second series, San Francisco, #5, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Canadian Poetry Magazine, Toronto, Canada, v. 11, #1, September, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Canadian Poetry Magazine, Toronto, Canada, v. 11, #3, March, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Canadian Poetry Magazine, Toronto, Canada, v. 26, #2, February, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Canto, Los Angeles, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- The Cape Rock, Southeast Missouri State University, Cape Girardeau, Missouri, v. 11, #2, Summer, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Carcanet, Oxford, England, Winter, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Caryatid, New Orleans, v. 2, #1, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
- The Cat Mousam Journal, Gorham, Maine, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
- The Cat Mousam Journal, Gorham, Maine, v. 1, #3, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Center, Woodstock, New York, #2, July, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Center, Woodstock, New York, #3, April, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Change, Detroit, #2, Spring/Summer, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- The Changes, Oakland, California, #3, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- The Changes, Oakland, California (Almanac of the Changes, Glenellen, California), 1967-1978 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Changes, Bisbee, Arizona, #2, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Chelsea, New York City, #22-23, June, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Chelsea, New York City, #24-25, October, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Cheval D'Attaque, France, #1, January, 1969-February, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Chicago, Chicago, v. 1, #1, February, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Chicago, Chicago, v. 5, #1, November, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Chicago, Chicago, v. 6, March, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Chicago, Chicago, European Edition, #2 (Wivenhoe, England), February, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Chicago Choice, Chicago, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Chrysalis Review, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Cinquefoil, Allen Park, Michigan, #3, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Circular Causation, Vancouver, Canada, #2, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Circular Causation, Vancouver, Canada, #3 (Georgia Straight Supplement), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- City, New York City, #2, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- City, New York City, #4, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- City Lights Journal, San Francisco, #1, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- City Lights Journal, San Francisco, #2, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- City Lights Journal, San Francisco, #3, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Cloud Marauder, Oakland, California, #3, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Cloud Marauder, Oakland, California, #6, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Coastlines, Hollywood, California, v. 5, #1 (#17), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Cobblestone, Emerson College, Boston, Spring, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Collection, Hove, England, #3, January, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Collection, Hove, England, #4 (and Tzarad 3), April, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Collection, Hove, England, #6 (and Tzarad 4) (The August August), November, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- College Poetry Review, Los Angeles, Fall, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Concept, Woodbridge, England, #6, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Concours, Westminster College, Salt Lake City, #2, April 5, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Connections, Putnam Valley, New York, #3, Fall, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Connections, Putnam Valley, New York, #4, Winter, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Con Safos, Los Angeles, v. 1, #3, March, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Consumption, Seattle, v. 1, #4, Summer, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Consumption, Seattle, v. 2, #4, Summer, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Consumption, Seattle, v. 3, #1-2 (The Whites of Their Eyes), March, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Contact II, New York City, v. 1, #1, November, 1976-December, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Contact II, New York City, v. 1, #2, January, 1977-February, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Contour, Berkeley, California, v. 1, #1, April, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Contour, Berkeley, California, #2, September, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Contraband, Portland, Maine, #5, May 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Contraband, Portland, Maine, #10, September, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Contraband, Portland, Maine, #12, February, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Corduroy, Bristol, Tennessee, #8, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Cosmos, Micklegate, England, #1, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Cosmos, Micklegate, England, #2, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Cosmos, Micklegate, England, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Cottonwood Review, University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas, #1, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Cottonwood Review, University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas, Spring, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Cottonwood Review, University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas, Fall, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Cow, San Francisco, "Cow Soup Issue", circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Coyote's Journal, Eugene, Oregon, #2, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Coyote's Journal, Eugene, Oregon, #3 (In Honeytown, William Brown), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Coyote's Journal, Eugene, Oregon, #7 (New Sharon's Prospect & Journal, Theodore Enslin, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Crab Grass, Belfast, Northern Ireland, #3, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Critique, Champaign, Illinois, #2, February, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Cronopios, La Crosse, Wisconsin, #2, April, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cronopios, La Crosse, Wisconsin, #4 (Say My Name, Barbara Gibson), October, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Crosscurrents, University of Puget Sound, Tacoma, Washington, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Crucible, Auckland, New Zealand, Summer, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Crucible, Utah State University, Logan, Utah, v. 12, Spring, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Crucified Toad, Manchester, England, #1, Winter, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Curtains, Maidstone, England, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Dacotah Territory, Moorehead, Minnesota, v. 1, #1, January, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Dacotah Territory, Moorehead, Minnesota, #3, Summer, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Daily Planet, "V.S.H. House Organ", New York City, #2, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Damascus Road, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)